[Music]
working at Prudential was transformity
for
me I was a person filled with
uncertainty and I wasn't confident or
sure of my own
abilities I remember the day my friend
passed away from
cancer I saw the horrors of having no
support and that's why I prioritized
protection above of everything
else I found myself here I had to step
out and help
others this is my calling I want to make
sure that other people are
covered I would hope for anybody to do
the same find your calling and you will
help others along the
[Music]
way I constantly set my own goals and I
focus on reaching them like making sure
they I truly understand my
clients this is especially so because I
have made a midc career
switch people often feel a b Mo like
that but what you want is outside of
your comfort
zone if you want it you do it if you
start right you will end in the right
[Music]
path
I've seen my customer gone through
several phase in
life from Marriage to having home to
having kids it is natural to have
anxiety to Def phrase I'm there to help
them stay in their course I've been told
that in a way I'm like their
[Music]
coach mdrt is certainly a
recognition but it is more important
important to find meaning in my
job and for me I get personal
satisfaction when I'm able to help my
customer achieve their
[Music]
Milestones I am CJ I join credential in
2021 and I'm a c of the table
qualifier my name is Jesse I beat a mid
CER s and this is my third year
qualifying for
MDT my name is Joe I qualified for MDT
for 12 times and I believe consistency
is
[Music]
key